(
"ai_sub_version": "1.10.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
hololive 3rd Generation Live
きゅるるん大作戦〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
Kyururun Great Operation: The Strongest Idols, You Just Have to Support Them
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon
Attention
ご来場のお客様へ
To all guests in attendance
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK
2次販売グッズ
Secondary Sale Goods
グッズ販売期間
1.14 20:00〜2.24 18:00
Goods Sale Period
Jan 14, 20:00 – Feb 24, 18:00
hololive 3rd Generation Live きゅるるん大作戦
hololive 3rd Generation Live: Operation Kyururun
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
2次販売グッズ
2nd Round Goods
だいすき だいすき だいすき だいすき だいすき だいすき！
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you!
溢れるこの愛きっと止まらない
This overflowing love surely won't stop.
たくさんの素敵なショート動画ありがとうございました！
Thank you for many wonderful short videos!
ぜひ音ありでお楽しみください！
Please enjoy with sound!
素敵なショート動画ありがとうございました！ぜひ『あいあい♡あいらぶゆー』を使って動画を作ってみてください！
Thank you for the wonderful short videos! Please try making a video using "Aiai ♡ I Love You"!
あいあい♡あいらぶゆー
Aiai ♡ I Love You
もっと もっと
More, more
好きなだけ愛させて
Let me love you as much as I want
ゆめみるハートがぴょんぴょん
My dreaming heart is jumping around
穴に落ちて あーみゃみゃ
Falling into a hole, ah-myamya
こんなになってもいまだ抜け出せない
Even now, I still can't get out
どうしたもんかな ぬいぬいぬい
What should I do? Nui nui nui
助けて君たち あほいほい
Help me, you guys, ahoy-hoi
もっと もっと もっと
More, more, more
好きなだけ愛してね
Love me as much as you want
きゅるるん大作戦 〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
Kyururun Great Strategy ~The strongest idols, you have no choice but to support them~
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon...
Please wait a moment until the performance begins
Sponsors 協賛
Sponsors
アニメにハマって、歌いたくなっちゃった。
I got hooked on anime, and now I want to sing!
推しのシーン見ながらカラオケ歌えるなんて...
To be able to sing karaoke while watching scenes of my favorite character...
尊すぎて辛いっ！
It's so precious, it hurts!
歌いたいアニメ・アニソン見つけよう！
Let's find the anime and anime songs you want to sing!
JOYSOUND どアニメ宣言！
JOYSOUND Do-Anime Sengen!
全国のアミューズメント施設にて
ホロライブ3期生 プライズ順次展開中！
Hololive 3rd Gen prizes are now being released
at amusement facilities nationwide!
全国のアミューズメント施設でGETしてね！
Get them at amusement facilities nationwide!
FuRyu
吉野家でごはんしょ♪
Let's eat at Yoshinoya♪
吉野家でお祝いしよ！
Let's celebrate at Yoshinoya!
ぎゅう。
Gyu.
ぎゅうぎゅう。
Gyu-gyu.
ぎゅう。
Gyu.
元祖の本気、召し上がれ。
Please enjoy the true dedication of the original.
牛丼は吉野家。
For beef bowls, it's Yoshinoya.
やっぱこれだね。
This is the one, after all.
きゅるるん大作戦〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
Operation Kyururun: The Ultimate Idols—You Have No Choice But to Support Them!
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
2次販売グッズ
2nd Release Goods
本日は、ホロライブ...
Today, Hololive...
ホロライブ3期生ライブ、
Hololive 3rd Generation Live,
『きゅるるん大作戦〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜』DAY2に
“Kyururun Daisakusen: The Strongest Idols, You Gotta Support 'Em” DAY 2.
ご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming today!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、
In order to enjoy the live until the end,
いくつかご案内させていただきます。
I'll give you a few announcements.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, recording, or filming during the performance is strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。
Smoking is prohibited inside the building.
喫煙はご遠慮ください。
Please refrain from smoking.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は無理をせず、
In the event that you feel unwell, please don't overexert yourself
近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
and inform a nearby staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、
Moshing, diving, or throwing things onto the stage within the venue,
他の皆さんの迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
and any behavior that causes trouble or interferes with the performance is strictly forbidden.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Please follow the rules and have a great time!
おーっ！
Whooo!
聞こえるね。うん。
I can hear them. Yeah.
また、本公演は映像配信及び写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、
Also, cameras for video streaming and photography are present in the venue,
客席が映り込む場合があります。
and the audience seating may be captured.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに
These videos and photos may be used
使用される可能性がありますので、あらかじめご了承ください。
for promotional purposes, so please be aware of this in advance.
おーっ！
Oh!
また、ライブのハッシュタグは『#きゅるるん大作戦DAY2』です。
The hashtag for the live is #KyururunDaisakusenDAY2.
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてください！
Please use the hashtag and get everyone excited!
盛り上げてー！
Get excited!
それでは開演まであと少しです。
It's almost time for the show to start.
君たちの声をいっぱい聞かせてください！
Let us hear your voices loud and clear!
そして、今からちょっと3期生で円陣を組もうと思っているんですが、
And now, we 3rd generation members are going to do a huddle cheer,
えっと、マイクを通さずやりますので、
but we'll be doing it without microphones,
ちょっと静かにして耳を澄ませていただければと思います。
so please be quiet and listen closely.
行くんで、ちょっとシーンと待っててください。静かにね！
We're starting, so please wait in silence. Be quiet, okay!
いきます！
Here we go!
ぺこら！フレア！
Pekora! Flare!
ノエル！マリン！
Noel! Marine!
ホロライブ3期生、きゅるるん大作戦！
Hololive 3rd Gen, Operation Kyururun!
おーーーーいくぞーー！！
Oooooh, let's go!!
こんぺこ！
Konpeko!
兎田ぺこら
(USADA PEKORA)
Usada Pekora
不知火フレア
(SHIRANUI FLARE)
Shiranui Flare
こんまっする！
Konmassuru!
白銀ノエル
(SHIROGANE NOEL)
Shirogane Noel
Ahoy!
宝鐘マリン
(HOUSHOU MARINE)
Houshou Marine
#きゅるるん大作戦
〜最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ〜
#Kyururun Daisakusen
~The Strongest Idols, You Can't Help But Stan~
超アイドル 3rdのガールは 欲張り
Super idols, we 3rd Gen girls are greedy
笑い合ってもっと可愛くなる
We'll get even cuter as we laugh together
Oh yeah yeah
遠い遠いお出かけだって
Even when we're going far, far away
4人なのにお家みたいで
The four of us feel just like home
だるだるなテンション
Lazy, relaxed vibes
くるるん大作戦
Kururun big strategy
喜怒哀楽はシェアしてさ
Sharing all our ups and downs
大きくなっていきたいよね でも小さなことも大事にして
We want to grow big, but we'll treasure the small things too
一つ一つ刻んでく
Carving out each and every moment
楽しんでくれるのが嬉しい
It makes us happy when you enjoy it
最高のエンターテイナー
As the ultimate entertainers
後ろまで見えてるよ
We can see all the way to the back
画面の向こうも届いてる
And we're reaching those beyond the screen
光の海を泳ごう
Let's swim through this sea of light
超アイドル 3rdのガールは 欲張り
Super idols, we 3rd Gen girls are greedy
愛されたいし 夢乗せたいし 君とじゃなきゃやだ
We want to be loved, share our dreams, it has to be with you
絶好調です 狙い撃ちで 君にウインク
We're in top form, aiming a wink right at you
やっぱ3rdのガールで めっちゃハッピー
As 3rd Gen girls, we're super happy after all
お嫁したいし 声出したいし 叶っちゃうやだ
Want to be brides, want to shout, oh it's coming true!
全力走る 勿論君と
Running at full speed, of course with you
笑い合ってもっと可愛くなる
We'll get even cuter as we laugh together
Oh yeah yeah
せっかくだからやり切りたいし 乗り越えるべき壁もデカい
Since we're here, we want to go all out, even the walls to climb are huge
そうさうんとエンタメて
That's right, with lots of entertainment
君が思ってるよりずっと 君のことを想ってる
Way more than you think, we're thinking about you
どうかな 焦がれた 夢には近づけてるかな
I wonder, are we getting closer to the dreams we longed for?
みんなの声があるから頑張れるんだ 聞かせて
One, two, three, four!
We can do our best because we have your voices. Let us hear it!
超最高 3rdのガールは 幸せ
Super awesome, we 3rd Gen girls are happy
愛されて行ける場所があって 下向くとかやだ
Having a place to go where we're loved, looking down is a no-no
テンポアップし 続けていくよ
We'll keep on picking up the tempo
見たい景色へ
To the scenery we want to see
世界に出せ! L-O-V-E
Show it to the world! L-O-V-E
光呼び出せ! L-O-V-E
Call out the light! L-O-V-E
今すぐ足せ! L-O-V-E
Add it right now! L-O-V-E
みんなで作ってく! Yeah!
Creating it together with everyone! Yeah!
もっともっと盛り上がっていくぞー！
Let's get even more hyped up!
君たち、まだまだ声出せますよねー！
You guys, you can still let your voices out, right?!
ユライデモ
Even if it wavers...
ガンバッチャ
...I'll keep trying.
褒められて伸びるはわかってるよね
You know I'm the type who thrives on praise, right?
ほの暗さが宝物
The dimness is a treasure.
練っちゃわないよ（笑）
I'm not going to sleep on it (Laughs)
君と一緒に！
Together with you!
超愛ドル天のガールは欲張り
The Super-Idol Ten-no-Girl is greedy.
愛されたい 夢も見てみたい
I want to be loved, I want to dream.
君じゃなきゃ
It has to be you.
ヤバって超絶 ネガイ撃ちで君にウインク
It's crazy, super... Shooting my wish with a wink to you.
やっぱ天のガールでめっちゃハッピー
As expected, I'm super happy being a Ten-no-Girl.
あれもしたいし これもしたいし
I want to do that, and I want to do this.
叶っちゃう
They'll come true.
やっぱ天と走る もちろん君と笑い合って
As expected, running with Ten... Of course, laughing with you.
もっと可愛くなる
I'll become even cuter.
どこまででも行けちゃう気がする
I feel like I can go anywhere.
Oh yeah yeah
今日はこのままサヨナラじゃないよ
Today isn't just goodbye like this.
手を取ってくれたなら
If you would only take my hand.
秘密も眠りにつくような夜に
In the kind of night where even secrets go to sleep,
君を連れてくよ
I'll take you away.
それは例えば遠く離れてたって
For instance, even if we're far apart,
手を繋いでいられるような
Like we can stay holding hands,
奇跡のような
Like a miracle...
話をしよう 窓はあけといて
Let's talk. Leave the window open.
今日までを思い出して
Remembering everything until today.
ひとつひとつ並べたら
When I line them up one by one,
明日の雨が気になりだして
I start worrying about tomorrow's rain.
どうも眠れないみたいだ
It seems I just can't sleep.
変わりたくないことや
Things I don't want to change,
変わらなきゃいけないことも
And things that have to change...
少し忘れたまま窓の外
While forgetting them a bit, outside the window,
眺めていたんだ
I was gazing.
あぁ 雨が降り出すその前に
Ah, before the rain starts falling,
君のところまで行けるような
I feel like I can reach your place,
気がして
So...
目を閉じてみたんだ
I tried closing my eyes.
そして
And then...
このまま遠くへ行こう
Let's go far away like this.
手を取ってくれるかな
I wonder if you'll take my hand.
秘密も眠りにつくような夜を
Through the kind of night where even secrets go to sleep,
君と泳いでいくよ
I'll swim along with you.
街の明かりが消えるたびに笑って
Laughing every time the city lights go out,
路地裏で抱き合おう
Let's embrace in the back alley.
バカみたいな
Like a fool,
話をしよう 窓はあけといて
Let's talk. Leave the window open.
聞こえる
I can hear it.
次はマリン！
Next is Marine!
君たち、2日目も盛り上がっていきますよ〜！
You guys, let's get fired up for day 2 as well!
言い訳バニー！
Iiwake Bunny!
どっちが好きなのよ！
Which one do you like?!
なんとかかんないかな
Can't we do something about this?
ラビラビ 隣のあいつが邪魔だな
Lovi-lovi, that person next to me is in the way.
ROUND 01 VS
やめてそんなこと
Stop that.
ダメダメダメ 前提必勝 絶対
No, no, no. Absolute victory is a prerequisite.
ドワドワ 違うな なんて競争
Dwa-dwa, that's wrong. What a competition.
苦手さ そういうの
I'm not good at that kind of thing.
ROUND 02 VS
なんだか寂しい
Somehow it's lonely.
ジマジママシン
Jima-jima machine.
無視してシークレット
Ignore it, secret.
ペンぺレ・シークレット
Pen-pere secret.
あの子にゃ負けない
I won't lose to that girl.
噂だってジェラシー
Even the rumors are jealous.
欲張りね 欲張りか？
Greedy, aren't you? Or am I the greedy one?
してやりますよ！
I'll show you!
言わなきゃってわかってる
I know I have to say it.
あーでもない こーでもない
It's not this, it's not that.
やめにしましょう
Let's stop.
つらるるまい まい まい まい
I won't be lured, my, my, my, my.
聞きたくない
I don't want to hear it.
言い訳バニー
Iiwake Bunny.
ジラジラの優柔不断
Fidgety indecision.
ダンダダン
Dan-da-dan.
ハニーバニーだりだり マジな話
Honey Bunny, dari-dari. Seriously.
どっち？
Which one?
どっちが好きなのよ！
Which one do you like?!
ダメダメダメダメ
No, no, no, no.
よそ見しないで
Don't look away.
ダメダメダメ
No, no, no.
抜け出したい
I want to break free.
今日は私の方でしょでしょ
Today it's my turn, right? Right?
どうしまして反対方向
You're welcome, in the opposite direction.
One Two
言い訳バニー
Iiwake Bunny.
息つく暇ない
No time to catch my breath
言い訳ばかり
Nothing but excuses
地団駄の優柔不断
Stamping feet in indecision
Honey bunny ガリガリ真面目な話
Honey bunny, a dead serious talk
どっちどっちが好きなのよ
Which one, which one do you like?
ダメダメダメ よそ見しないで
No no no, don't look away
ダメダメダメ もう逃げ出したい
No no no, I want to run away
喧嘩やるしかない
Nothing to do but fight
いっしょにどっしり反対方向
Together, let's take a hard turn in the opposite direction!
WANTED!
言い訳ばかり
Nothing but excuses
そばにいて言い訳ばかり
Be by my side, nothing but excuses
次は、ぺこーら！
Next up, Pekora!
全力ジャンピング！イッツ・オール・オッケー！
Full power jumping! It's All Okay!
でも絵本描きたくなしで
Without even a closing page for the picture book
歌いながら気の向く方へ
Singing towards wherever my heart leads
迷ってるの？冒険してるの？
Are you lost? Are you adventuring?
それはみんな次第
That's up to everyone
まだまだ楽しみ足りない
I still haven't had enough fun
でもでも時間が足りない
But, but time isn't enough
ワクワクする明日へ
Towards an exciting tomorrow
思い切り張り切って
Giving it my absolute all
前向いてさ進もう
Look forward and let's move on
せーの！歌って本気で
One, two! Sing seriously
リズムになっちゃえ
Get into the rhythm
遊びじゃくらいで It's All Okay
As if it were just a game, it's all okay
早起きよりも余白を
Rather than waking up early, leave some space
何とかなっちゃうはずだから
Because it should work out somehow
ピンチはチャンスになるから
Because a pinch becomes a chance
みんなで笑えば無敵だね
If we laugh together, we're invincible
何だって全力で
Whatever it is, with all our might
リズムになっちゃえ
Get into the rhythm
まっすぐな気持ちで行こう
Let's go with straightforward feelings
ホップステップで飛び出さ
Hop, step, and fly out
なかなかお布団から出られない日もある
There are days when I just can't get out of bed
demo明日から そう明日から
But from tomorrow, yes, from tomorrow
本気を出すんだ
I'll get serious
日が射すまで 日が暮れるまで
Until the sun shines, until the sun sets
無限の楽しみで
With infinite fun
It's All Okay
早起きよりも余白を
Rather than waking up early, leave some space
何とかなっちゃうはずだから
Because it should work out somehow
ピンチはチャンスになるから
Because a pinch becomes a chance
みんなで笑えば無敵だね
If we laugh together, we're invincible
何だって全力で
Whatever it is, with all our might
リズムになっちゃえ
Get into the rhythm
まっすぐな気持ちで行こう
Let's go with straightforward feelings
ホップステップで飛び出さ
Hop, step, and fly out
最後は、ノエル！
Last but not least, Noel!
はーい！みんな！シャッフルメドレー、最後まで盛り上がっていくぞー！
Yes! Everyone! Let's keep the energy up for the shuffle medley until the end!
苦い恋の果て
At the end of a bitter love
残された出所不明の金の山
A mountain of gold left behind from an unknown source
あいつの気配がするものは
Things that feel like him
未練ばかりで食えやしない
Are only regrets and aren't edible
アタシは生きながら
While I live
化けて出る鏡の前で早変わり
I'll appear as a ghost and transform quickly in front of the mirror
パイパイ仮面でどうかして
How about the Pai Pai Kamen?
今宵も一暴れ
Let's run wild tonight too
踊れ踊り踊れ
Dance, dance, dance
乱れ髪はずむ胸
Dishevelled hair and a beating heart
匿名（とくめい）の罠に酔いしれて
Intoxicated by the anonymous trap
Shy Spot!
Shy Spot! ライト・ミー・ナ
Shy Spot! Light me up
ヤヤヤ
Ya ya ya
パパパヤパイ
Pa-pa-pa-ya-pai
パイパイ仮面は大富豪
Pai Pai Kamen is a multi-millionaire
ヤヤヤ
Ya ya ya
パパパヤパイ
Pa-pa-pa-ya-pai
黄金の蝶 舞い上がれ
Golden butterfly, soar up
ほらほら
Look, look
踊れよ
Come on and dance
千番万歳 恋シャワー
A million cheers, a love shower
せせ
One, two
せーの お生きろよ
Three, live it out!
瞬間クライマックス
Instant climax
うう
Forget
浮世忘れて更ける
Forget the floating world and immerse
Discothequeに
In the discotheque
パイパイ仮面
Pai Pai Kamen
黄金の蝶　舞い上がれ
Let the golden butterfly fly high
魔法　踊れよ
Dance, with magic
三財万歳　恋シャワー
Banzai for spending, a shower of love
ルナ　生きろよ
Luna, live your life
春花クライマックス
Spring flowers reaching their climax
浮世忘れてぶっ飛ばせ DASH AND HIGH
Forget the floating world and fly away, DASH AND HIGH
早いわ　早いわ
It's fast, so fast
DISCO DECO QUICK　バイバイ仮面
DISCO DECO QUICK, bye bye mask
イエーイ！
Yeah!
DAY2！
Day 2!
DAY2ですよ！
It's Day 2!
DAY2だー！
じゃあ早速自己紹介からしていきますか？
Shall we start with the introductions right away?
していきましょう！
Let's do it!
はい！
Okay!
じゃあみんな、ぺこら久しぶりのあの挨拶行くから
Then everyone, Pekora's going to do her long-awaited signature greeting,
分かるよねみんな？　あの挨拶だよ！
you all know it, right? It's that greeting!
どの挨拶だ？
Which one is it?
あれだ！
That one!
あれしかない！
It can only be that one!
いくぞー！
Here I go!
ドドンガドンドン、全人類Vチューバー、
Dodonga don don, for all humanity V-Tuber,
全人、全V...　ドドン...　大丈夫か！？
all huma, all V... Dodon... Are you okay?!
もう一回、もう一回ね！
One more time, one more time!
もう一度ね！
One more try!
行きます！
Here I go!
ドドンガドンドン、全Vチューバー一
Dodonga don don, who is the number one
超絶可愛いのは誰だ！？　ドドンガドンドン！
super cute V-Tuber of all?! Dodonga don don!
ぺこらちゃーん！
Pekora-chan!
やっとできましたー！
I finally did it!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
はい！
Okay!
じゃあ次はフレアちゃん！
Next up is Flare-chan!
はい！　じゃあフレアは「はいダーリン！」って言うので
Okay! I'll say "Hi Darling!",
「はいハニー！」って返してください！　オッケー？
so please respond with "Hi Honey!" Okay?
行きますよー！　はいダーリン！
Here I go! Hi Darling!
はいハニー！
Hi Honey!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
ホロライブ3期生、不知火フレアです！
I'm Shiranui Flare from Hololive 3rd Gen!
そして？
And next?
はい！　えー、どうしようかな今日...
Yes! Um, what should I do today...
あ、じゃあ「こんまっする」って言うから普通に「こんまっする」で...
Oh, I'll say "Konmassuru", so just say "Konmassuru" back...
「こんまっする」でいいのか？
Is "Konmassuru" good enough?
いや、牛丼もね...
Well, beef bowls too...
牛丼は、まあまあ...
Beef bowls are... okay, I guess...
あ、やばい、やばい！
Oh no, oh no!
あばあばあばあば...
Aba-aba-aba-aba...
よし、行くぞ！
Alright, here I go!
せーの、こんまっするー！
Ready, set... Konmassuru!
こんまっするー！
Konmassuru!
はい！　ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルです！
Yes! I'm Shirogane Noel from Hololive 3rd Gen!
よいしょー！　はい！　そして？
Yoisho! Yes! And next?
君たち！　本物のパイパイ仮面は誰！？
You guys! Who is the real Pai Pai Mask?!
マリンー！
Marine!
なんかマリン、一度も言ってないけど
Even though Marine hasn't said it once,
パイパイ仮面、パイパイ仮面って...
everyone is shouting "Pai Pai Mask, Pai Pai Mask"...
なんか昨日からさ、ぺこらに船長取られるし
Since yesterday, Pekora took the title of Captain,
ノエルにパイパイ仮面取られるし、本物のパイパイ仮面なんだけどな！
and Noel took the Pai Pai Mask, even though I'm the real one!
本物のパイパイ仮面として暴れたいわけですね！
So you want to go wild as the real Pai Pai Mask!
悲しい。ということでね！
How sad. So, anyway!
はーい、あほーい！　ホロライブ3期生宝鐘海賊団船長の宝鐘マリンです！
Ahoy! I'm the Captain of the Houshou Pirates, Houshou Marine from Hololive 3rd Gen!
いや、ついにDAY2！
Wow, finally Day 2!
DAY2ですよ！
It's Day 2!
なんか昨日と衣装違くない？
Doesn't our outfit look different from yesterday?
ね！
Right!
あれ、分かりましたか皆さん！
Oh, did everyone notice!
なんか昨日とちょっと...
It's a bit different from yesterday...
悪魔になっちゃった！
We've become devils!
あら！　天使から悪魔っぽくなってしまったかな？
Oh! Have we turned from angels to devilish ones?
そうなんですよね！
That's right!
実はこれ、初めて公開するんですよね！
Actually, this is the first time we're revealing this!
そうなんですよ！
Yes, it is!
みんなびっくりしたかな？
I wonder if everyone was surprised?
可愛ーい！
So cute!
可愛ーい！　ありがとー！
So cute! Thank you!
え、でも悪魔なんか、結構マリンは小悪魔系で売ってるんで
But as for being a devil, Marine is already marketed as a little devil type,
かなりシナジーあるかなって！
so I think there's a lot of synergy!
だってぺこらも小悪魔系で売ってるからシナジー...
Well, Pekora is also marketed as a little devil, so synergy...
お前は悪魔鳥だよ、悪魔鳥！
You're a devil bird, a devil bird!
小悪魔...
Little devil...
なんか、そんなの...
Something like that...
うぉーーー！
Wooooh!
変な悪魔いかない？
Isn't there a weird devil?
嫌な奴だもの。
What a nuisance.
天使と悪魔、どっちが好き、君たち？
Which do you guys like better, angels or devils?
あ、確かに！
Oh, true!
じゃあ「はい」で言ってもらえば、「天使の人」って言って...
Then let's have them respond with "Yes", for example when I say "those who like angels"...
え、ペンライト！
Um, penlights!
ペンライトの色とかあったかな？
Were there specific penlight colors?
白と赤！
White and red!
悪魔！
Devil!
じゃあ、悪魔派は赤！
Then, for the devil faction, use red!
赤。天使派は白！
Red. For the angel faction, white!
白。の方！
White. That's the one!
じゃあ行くか！
Let's go then!
じゃあ皆さん変えてください！
Everyone, please change your colors!
掲げてください！
Hold them up!
あ、でも結構いい感じに割れてる！
Oh, it's divided pretty evenly!
若干赤が多い？
Is red slightly more common?
チェッ！
Tsk!
あれ、悪魔の方が人気？
Huh, is the devil more popular?
あ、でもなんか半々かも！
Oh, but it might be fifty-fifty!
すげー割れてるね！
It's really split!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
え、じゃあ今日いいわね、悪魔な感じも！
Well, today is great, including the devilish vibe!
これを見られて良かったね、ぺこら！
It was good to see this, Pekora!
DAY1に引き続き、バンドも生演奏となってまーす！
Continuing from Day 1, the band is performing live!
ありがとー！
Thank you!
ちょっとカッコいいですね、これね
This is pretty cool, isn't it?
カッコいい！
Cool!
ありがとうございます
Thank you very much.
嬉しいですよ
I'm happy.
そして配信のコメントももちろん見てます
And of course I'm watching the stream comments too.
見てるよ、みんな！
I see you, everyone!
もうもちろん会場のみんなももちろんアツアツだよ！
And of course everyone at the venue is fired up too!
見てるよ、みんな！
I see you, everyone!
すごいみんな素敵な気合いの入った推し活ファッションしてきてくれてありがとう！
Thank you all for coming in such wonderful, spirited fan outfits!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
カワイイ！
So cute!
最高、最高ですよ
It's the best, simply the best.
最高ですね
It's the best, isn't it?
いやもうちょっぱなね、シャッフルメドレーでしたけど
Man, we had a shuffle medley right from the start.
ヤバかったよね！
It was insane, wasn't it?
ヤバかったですよね！
It really was insane!
アゲアゲ
So hyped.
でもですね、なんとですね、ここまでで…
But, you know, it turns out that...
え？え？
What? What?
冒頭無料チラ見せが
the opening free preview
終了となります！
ends here!
嘘でしょ！そんな！
No way! Really?!
うそだー！嘘でしょ！？
You're lying! No way!
嘘ぺこでしょ、きた
Here we go, "it's a lie, peko."
そうなんですね、嘘ではないぺこです
That's right, but it's not a lie, peko.
そうなの
That's how it is.
みんな見たいと思ってくれてると思うから、概要欄に配信チケットリンクあるので
I think everyone wants to see more, so the link for stream tickets is in the description.
今ポチポチっと買ってみてください
Please go ahead and buy one right now.
お願いします！
Please!
後悔させない！
You won't regret it!
今日はすごい、今日もすごい、今日が一番すごい
Today is amazing, today is also amazing, today is the most amazing.
またすごくなってるね
It's gotten even better again.
もうブチ上げブチ上げで準備ですから
We're all set to pump things up to the max.
Day 1 とは違ったね、盛り上がり
The excitement was different from Day 1.
もう君たちも今日超ブチ上がりなんで
You guys are also super hyped today.
頑張って最後まで息切れしないようにブチ上がってください！
So do your best and keep that energy up until the end without running out of breath!
最高だ！
Awesome!
しっかり声出してね！
Make sure to shout loud!
出してね！
Shout it out!
そして配信で楽しんでる人は
And for those of you enjoying the stream...
あのハッシュタグ #きゅるるん大作戦DAY2 にいっぱい呟いてください！
please tweet a lot using the hashtag #KyururunDaisakusenDay2!
お願いします！
Please!
はい、はい、ふぅ、ふぅ
Alright, alright, phew, phew.
じゃあドキドキするね
Well, my heart's racing.
そろそろいいですか？
Is it about time?
行きますか！
Shall we go?
次の曲に行ってもよろしいでしょうか？
May we move on to the next song?
行っちゃいましょう！
Let's go for it!
それではですね、次の曲はなんと私からスタートさせていただきます！
Well then, the next song will actually start with me!
なにが来るんだろう、なんだろう、なんだろう
I wonder what's coming, what could it be?
それじゃあ次の曲行きましょう！
Well then, let's go to the next song!
クリアメドレー！
Clear Medley!
イェーイ！
Yay!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!